♪~
This way, this way, this way, this way, this way, this way, this way, this way, this way, this way, this way.
What I can do now
I'll do my best
I'll think about it again tomorrow
Today, I'd like to teach you
I'd like to teach you how to swing a tune
Yes, sir!
This is a song that we're going to have a lot of fun dancing to.
We're going to have a lot of fun with this song.
Okay, let's get started!
Let's get right to it.
Okay.
Okay, let's do the first part of the lyrics.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, first of all, ma'am, do you know your pose?
Here.
Bring it to the temple light.
Ready?
~~
What do you do with it?
Pé
Pee.
This guy is
Kato-chan
pe
Pee.
Kato-chan
Pé
Pe.
After this Pe
Dotto dotto dotto dotto dotto
Yes, sir.
I think I should keep doing it up to here.
Let's do it.
Three, two, one, go.
~~
Kato-chan.
Phe
Dotto dotto dotto dotto dotto
Wonderful.
Excellent.
Thank you very much.
Let's go next
Again to the temple.
Do the same one again.
There you go.
~~
Aiin.
Ai.
And then...
~~
One more time
Yes, sir.
Ready
~~
It's great. It's great.
Excellent.
Applause
And then...
Right left hip
Right head
Right hip to left head
In
From the top
Which three three three three
In
four shoulders together
Yes
In
~~
Shake four times
And then
Do the Mr. Tork pose again on your templesDo the Mr. Tork pose again on your temples.
I'll take it out.
Fire.
Four times.
Keep it in front of you.
Awkward.
If it's awkward...
Think about it again tomorrow.
I'll think about it again tomorrow
And
To those who will think about it again tomorrow.
Why not?
Yes, why not?
Why?
Yes, sir.
I'll go first.
Okay.
♪
I'll ride shoulder-to-shoulder with you.
That's me now.
Fire.
Fire! Fire!
Awkward.
Yes, sir.
Do it from the beginning.
Start from the beginning
From the beginning
Can you do it?
Yes, sir.
All right.
~~
Shoulder to shoulder
Fire.
~~
I don't know why.
That's good.
It's good.
That's great.
All right, then.Let's get to it.
Let's dance to the music!
Let's dance to the music together!
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, sir.
We'll think of something else tomorrow.
At the end of the second chorus
Kawaoka-san's energy
at the end of the second chorus.
Why do you think
Kawaoka-san's energy
That's right.
Genki.
Here.
I want you to do this.
I want you to do what you think
Vigorous pose
Yes, sir.
Kawaoka-san's vigor
Cheerful
Yes, please try it
Yes, please do it.
Then, what do you think?
Cheerful pose
Yes, I do
Imitation
Three.
Two.
Excellent
Excellent.
Just like this.
You should all dance too.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you for watching.